A Guide to the Watkins Family Papers, ca. 1910-2000 (bulk ca. 1930-1960)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Photographs, 1910-1994, Extent: 1.4 cubic feet. (Box 1-5)
  - Photograph Album #7, Photos 34-74 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    44. School group in front of school bus. Includes Edna Brown, Mahalia Otey, Joan Christian, Eurcell Armstead, Eunice Carter, Ellen Ross, Marion Randolph, Patricia Johnson, Adell Minor, Lueitha Crump, Phyllis Morris, Viola Washington, Martha Crump, Helen Williams, and Clarice Moss, ca. 1950
    45. Mothers Day photograph of Gladys Taylor, Lillian Darby, and Thelma Watkins, 8 May 1988
    46. Gloria Ann Roane school photograph (age 6), ca. 1960
    47. Store front of Sedley D. Jones Furniture with two employees/owners, ca. 1920-1930
    48. Second Liberty Church Junior Choir, 1965
    49. School play at George W. Watkins School, ca. 1960
    50. Rhonda Delina Dailey school photograph (age 13), 1971
    51. Tia [Petty?] school photograph (age 6), 1975
    52. Maryetta school photograph (5th grade), 1979
    53. Rae school photograph, 1973-1974
    54. Cheryl school photograph (age 14), 1973-1974
    55. Rhonda school photograph (age 15), 1973-1974
    56. Anita Louise school photograph (age 10), ca. 1970
    57. Quincey Bryant school photograph (Marcella and Jackie's son), ca. 1970
    58. Edward III school photograph (age 13), 1973-1974
    59. Kerry Williams school photograph (age 9, 4th grade), 1971-1972
    60. Curry Williams school photograph (son of Antoinette and Rudolph), ca. 1970
    61. Letitia Williams school photograph (daughter of Antoinette and Rudolph), ca. 1970
    62. Anita Louise school photograph (age 11), ca. 1970
    63. Second Liberty Church, Mrs. Iola Burrell, teacher, ca. 1970
    64. Rhonda Delina school photograph (age 9), ca. 1970
    65. Tia Petty school photograph (age 7), 1976
    66. Jacquelin Bryant school photograph (daughter of Jack and Marietta), graduation Virginia Union University, May 1983
    67. Sylvia Winston school photograph, ca. 1980
    68. Sedley D. Jones III, 16 November 1985
    69. Possibly school play photograph, George W.Watkins School, ca. 1960
    70. Career Day George W. Watkins School. Leaders, Mrs. Smith, Business; Mrs. Gary, Nursing; Mrs. Gray, Dramatics; Miss Jones, Guest Speaker; Mrs. Crutchfield; Mrs. Craddock, and Mrs. Tyree, 24 May 1961
    71. School play, George W.Watkins School, ca. 1960
    72. Thelma Dixon Crist, Hugo Carl, and Thelma J. Watkins, ca. 1960
    73. Unidentified man on couch, ca. 1960
    74. Outdoor family photograph, ca. 1960
  - Photograph Album #7, Photos 75-104 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    75. Elsie Spurlock, Gladys Storrs, ca. 1920-1930
    76. Azelia Starrs Smith, ca. 1970
    77. Antoinette Brown (Quinton, Va.), 1970
    78. Unidentified woman in rocking chair, ca. 1960
    79. Joet Brown and 2 children (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1960
    80. Susie Brown (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1930
    81. Cheryl Cobb school photograph (age 5), 1966
    82. Helen Nicole Bolder school photograph, 1982
    83. Tonya Cobb school photograph (age 12), 1966
    84. Ella Jones, 1944
    85. Elderly women sitting, ca. 1960
    86. Marnie and Thomas Jones, 1964
    87. Unidentified building, nd
    88. Cheryl and Tonya Cobb, May 1978
    89. Mrs. Ada Davenport and son (Sunnybank, Va.), April 1963
    90. Unidentified woman (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1950
    91. Geraldine Walker (Philadelphia, Pa.), ca. 1950
    92. Seasons greetings photograph card from the Henderson family (Tom, Kate and T-Z), Virginia Union University, ca. 1950
    93. Photograph of building Charles Bowman lives in, 1955
    94. Sharon Baptist Church (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1960
    95. Gladys Dailey Petty graduation photograph, ca. 1960
    96. R.E.F. Washington family wedding, ca. 1960
    97. R.E.F. Washington family wedding, ca. 1960
    98. Unidentified school building, nd
    99. R.E.F. Washington family wedding, ca. 1960
    100. George Jefferson, 7 May 1950
    101. Unidentified woman and child in front of truck, ca. 1950
    102. Robert Prentis Daniel, ca. 1950
    103. Unidentified school building, nd
    104. Career Day, Mr. Dillard Counselor on Armed Forces, 24 March 1961
  - Photograph Album #7, Photos 105-125 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    105. Charles Bowman, somewhere in the woods of Alabama (my birthday), 22 February 1955
    106. Sharon Baptist Church (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1960
    107. Thelma J. Watkins, ca. 1960
    108. Perry Harvey, Deacon Third Union (King William, Va.), ca. 1960
    109. Two unidentified women in yard, ca. 1950
    110. Group of young men raking outside, ca. 1950
    111. Two women sitting at picnic table outside, ca. 1950
    112. Frankie Jr. and Pat, February 1952
    113. Group of women outside, ca. 1950
    114. Francis B. Cobb Jr., Christmas 1950
    115. Wedding couple, ca. 1950
    116. Gertye [unidentified], ca. 1940
    117. Diane Hawkins and Jamaal Hawkins, ca. 1970
    118. Andel and Isaac Meekin on wedding day, ca. 1950
    119. Group standing around, ca. 1970
    120. Man waving on bus, ca. 1940
    121. Group unidentified, ca. 1960
    122. Shelby Lynnette Belcher (age 5 1/2 months, granddaughter of Lloyd and Eryelia Otey) in Washington DC, 1959
    123. Little girl and two little boys outside of a house, ca. 1950
    124. Childrens Home Annual Day, 1968
    125. Seasons greeting card, ca. 1940
  - Photograph Album #8, Index key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photograph Album #8, Photos 1-31 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    1. Elderly woman opening present, 1997
    2. Thelma and George Watkins, ca. 1960
    3. Entrance to George W. Watkins School, 1968
    4. George W. Watkins friends in Carolina, family of a "best friend", ca. 1940
    5. Gentleman in glasses with hat in hand outside, ca. 1940
    6. Thelma J. Watkins as a baby, ca. 1920
    7. Tia Petty, Lillian Dailey, Gladys Taylor, Gladys Petty, and Thelma Watkins, ca. 1990
    8. Lillian Dailey and Gladys Taylor at Ester Thelma's, ca. 1990
    9. Group in dining room, June 1997
    10. Elaine Wilson school photograph (daughter of Liby Wilson), 1972
    11. Thelma Jones, Gladys, Mamie, Orr, ca. 1930
    12. Mrs. Storrs, mother of Gladys and Florence Storrs, ca. 1930
    13. J.W. Ned family, ca. 1970
    14. Mamie Frances Storrs, ca. 1930
    15. Gay Jones and Lillian Jones Dailey, ca. 1920
    16. Gay Jones and Thelma Jones, ca. 1940
    17. Ernest Watkins and Thelma Watkins, ca. 1950
    18. Charles Spurlock and Thelma Watkins, ca. 1960
    19. Thelma and George Watkins and child, ca. 1950
    20. Thelma Watkins, Andell Watkins, Ernest Watkins, ca. 1950
    21. Thelma J. Watkins on porch, c. 1960
    22. Thelma and George Watkins on steps of George W. Watkins School, ca. 1960
    23. Samuel Crump, 1st Negro Board of Supervisors in New Kent County, ca. 1950
    24. Samuel Crump, 1st Negro Board of Supervisors in New Kent County, ca. 1950
    25. Fifth Street home of Lena and Gay Jones (Richmond, Va.), nd
    26. George W. Watkins, Charles Williams, Janet Christian, and Cynthia Lewis, ca. 1970
    27. Thelma Watkins and Gladys Street, ca. 1960
    28. Thelma Watkins, ca. 1950
    29. Andel and Isaac Mickens, ca. 1940
    30. Birthday cakes for Thelma Watkins birthday made by Otis Jones, 1979, 1981, 1982
    31. Birthday cakes for Thelma Watkins birthday made by Otis Jones, 1979, 1981, 1982
  - Photograph Album #8, Photos 32-72 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    32. Four women in front of car, ca. 1960
    33. Postcard photograph of New Olive Grove Baptist Church (Central, SC), 1965
    34. Party for birthdays/anniversaries, ca. 1960
    35. Thelma Watkins, Dolly Christian, Montreat, and Louise, ca. 1960
    36. 100th Anniversary of Second liberty Baptist Church, nd
    37. 100th Anniversary of Second liberty Baptist Church, nd
    38. Unidentified couple, ca. 1970
    39. Letitia Williams, Lisa Williams, Antoinette Williams, ca. 1973
    40. Unidentified family, ca. 1970
    41. Ministers conference group (Charles City County, Va.), ca. 1970
    42. Unidentified group, ca. 1960
    43. Group in front of church including Lemuel Lewis, Willis Johnson, Frank Crump, Richard Davis, Lemuel Lewis Sr., John Wilkerson, and Lafayette Brown, ca. 1920
    44 Virginia Union University 60th class reunion (1926), Walter Daniel, Thelma Watkins, Willard Driver, and Lillian McWilliams, 1986
    45 Virginia Union University 65th class reunion (1926), Walter Daniel, Thelma Watkins, and Samuel Crump, 1991
    46. Lucille and Otis Jones, ca. 1970
    47. Hugo Curl and others in front of car, ca. 1940
    48. Dulenia Williams Bell and Thelma, ca. 1950
    49. "Taken in my back yard, The dog is a pure bred schipperke, cat a persian.," August 1963
    50. Unidentified couple, ca. 1970
    51. Unidentified woman in chair, ca. 1950
    52. Advertisement, nd
    53. Todd Dillard and wife, ca. 1950
    54. Marian Wallace Randall, Reverend Morris Randall and sister, baby granddaughter, ca. 1991
    55. Reverend Morris Randall, 1991
    56. Marian Wallace Randall, 1991
    57. Rebekah Burrell Cooke, Storrs, and other women, ca. 1970
    58. Unidentified family, ca. 1960
    59. Mamie Storrs, ca. 1960
    60. Edith Johnson Perry (Roanoke, Va.), 1988
    61. Doris Jefferson Washington, ca. 1970
    62. Dr. and Mrs. Franklin, Tom Jones, and Mr. Brown, ca. 1960
    63. Thelma Watkins and Gladys Street, ca. 1960
    64. Ruth, Lorraine, Ruby, and Emma Jefferson, ca. 1940
    65. Gladys Street, ca. 1950
    66. Advertisement, nd
    67. Baseball team (maybe T.C.L.A. Walker), ca. 1960
    68. Group of students, ca. 1960
    69. Group of teachers at dinner table, ca. 1960
    70. Group of cheerleaders, ca. 1960
    71. Clipping from The Tidewater-Review (West Point, Va.). George Washington honors Mrs. Septavia Crutchfield, supervisor of the New Kent County elementary schools retires, ca. 1970
    72. T.J. Watkins home, Bible prayer group. Includes Estelleta Davis, T. Watkins, Frank Christian, Edwin Basset, Milton Davis, Thomas Jefferson, and Anthony Green, 1985
  - Photograph Album #8, Photos 73-103 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    73. Group photograph of teachers from George W. Watkins School, 1963-1964
    74. Group on couch, ca. 1980
    75. Group on couch, ca. 1980
    76. Group on couch, ca. 1980
    77. Ella Cobbs, January 1992
    78. Tia graduation photograph, ca. 1990
    79. Unidentified school photograph, ca. 1990
    80. Thelma Watkins, ca. 1990
    81. Elam Ladies, Mrs. Smith, Mrs. Mamie Jones, Mrs. Cotman, Mrs. Beatrice Brown, Mrs. Cordelia Banks, and Miss Annie Franklin, ca. 1960
    82. Patricia Johnson on a visit while at home for holidays from St. Paul's College, 1960
    83. Michael Christian school photograph, 1982
    84. Seasons greeting photograph card of Herman and Inez and grandchildren Aaron and Tyisha, 1990
    85. Mamie Storrs Bell, ca. 1930
    86. Unidentified clipping
    87. Graduation with George W. Watkins, ca. 1960
    88. Arthur Christian, Thelma Watkins, and Doris Christian, ca. 1990
    89. Christmas photograph of Marietta Dailey Bryant, Jacquelin Bryant, Michael Bryant, and Quincy Bryant, ca. 1990
    90. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    91. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    92. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    93. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins. Includes Antoinette Williams, Marietta Bryant, and Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    94. Street sign George W. Watkins Road, June 1997
    95. Cheryl's daughter in New Jersey, January 1995
    96. Thelma Watkins outside house, June 1997
    97. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    98. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    99. Street sign of George W. Watkins Road, June 1997
    100. Group of ladies on couch, ca. 1990
    101. Christmas photograph, Frank and his 2 children, December 1994
    102. Tia Petty, ca. 1980
    103. Tombstone marker of Lillian D. Dailey (1910-1993), 1994
  - Photograph Album #8, Photos 104-132 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    104. George and Thelma Watkins, ca. 1960
    105. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, June 1997
    106. Tribute certificate to Thelma Jones Watkins, 25 May 1984
    107. Birthday party for Thelma Watkins, July 1999
    108. George W. Watkins retirement party, 1964
    109. George W. Watkins School faculty, 1964
    110. The Miles Mark - Ada Foster Fisher family, 1984
    111. Newspaper clipping on George W. Watkins retirement, 1964
    112. Newspaper clipping of an unidentified church, nd
    113. George W. Watkins, ca. 1960
    114. Newspaper clipping about George W. Watkins, in Tidewater Review, 14 March 1993
    115. Residence of Lina and Gay Jones (900 block, North 5th Street), nd
    116. Virginia Union University, Senior College Class photograph, 1926
    117. Virginia Union University, Summer Seminar, ca. 1960
    118. George W. Watkins retirement. Includes Superintendent Jennings, Mrs. Dillard, Mr. Dillard, Thelma Watkins, George Watkins, Mrs. Pearson, and Reverend Pearson, 1964
    119. George W. Watkins retirement. Includes Mrs. Dillard, Helen Watkins, Todd Dillard, Thelma Watkins, George Watkins, Louise Jackson Pearson, and Hugh Pearson, 1964
    120. George W. Watkins, ca. 1960
    121. Graduation photograph of Jettee Anderson, ca. 1960
    122. Gladys Petty look alike, nd
    123. Brochure from George W. Watkins Alumni & Scholastic Association, nd
    124. Newspaper clipping, Memories of Old St. Philip's (Richmond Free Press), 25-27 February 1993
    125. Elam Baptist Church invitation to 25th Wedding Anniversary of Mr. and Mrs. George W. Watkins, 20 November 1955
    126. Unidentified building
    127. Unidentified couple sitting on chair, ca. 1950
    128. Unidentified two women sitting on chair, ca. 1950
    129. George W. Watkins, ca. 1960
    130. Lillian Dailey graduation photograph, ca. 1960
    131. Thelma J. Watkins, ca. 1970
    132. Reverend J.H. Moody and daughter Jennie, ca. 1990
  - Photograph Album #9 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    1. Group of boys softball team, ca. 1960
    2. View inside of classroom, ca. 1960
    3. Unidentified minister preaching, ca. 1960
    4. Unidentified young man and woman, ca. 1960
    5. Myrtle Taylor, Jane Johnson, Patricia Johnson, Carolyn Wallace, and Kate Johnson at Reverend Easley's home in Lawrenceville, ca. 1960
    6. Delores Brown and Mr. Knight, ca. 1960
    7. Myrtle Taylor, Jane Johnson, Patricia Johnson, and Carolyn Wallace at Reverend Easley's home in Lawrenceville, ca. 1960
    8. Reverend and Mrs. Easley at home in Lawrenceville with Reverend and Mrs. Watkins and Alfred Brown, ca. 1960
    9. Robert and Bernice Johnson, ca. 1960
  - Photograph Album #10, Index key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 1-19 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    1. Unidentified woman at well, ca. 1940
    2. Unidentified woman on porch, ca. 1940
    3. George W. Watkins, ca. 1940
    4. George W. Watkins and children, ca. 1940
    5. Unidentified woman on bike, ca. 1940
    6. Group of school children, ca. 1930-1940
    7. Louise Ball, ca. 1940
    8. Two unidentified men, ca. 1940
    9. Group of school girls, ca. 1930-1940
    10. Group of teachers, ca. 1940: Louise Roane; Lelia Williams; Ethel Winningham; Louise Ball; Madge Sydnor; Mrs. Goodloe; Mrs. Bush; Jeannette Holland; Thelma Watkins; Mrs. Wood; Hattie Goodman; Miss Brown; Miss Banks; Miss Jones; Mrs. Smith; Mrs. Wright; Mrs. Cameron; Mrs. Furlong; Mrs. Stanley; Mrs. Gholson; Mrs. Morgan; Miss Holmes; Miss Roberts; Miss Rutledge; and Miss Williams.
    11. Antoinette Dailey, ca. 1940
    12. Graduation photograph of unidentified woman, ca. 1940-1950
    13. Albert Parham, James Charity; Thelma Watkins, Miss Foster; Thelma Fields; George W. Watkins, ca. 1940-1950
    14. Ernest Watkins, ca. 1950
    15. Gladys Poindexter, Thelma Watkins, George W. Watkins, unidentified man, ca. 1950
    16. Blanch Taylor Daniel, Ruby E. Dogan, Thelma Jones Watkins, Marian Stewart, ca. 1940
    17. Thelma and George W. Watkins, ca. 1940-1950
    18. Unidentified man, ca. 1950
    19. Unidentified children on porch, ca. 1940
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 20-36 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    20. Unidentified group, ca. 1940
    21. Unidentified woman, ca. 1940
    22. Unidentified woman, ca. 1940
    23. Gwendolyn Gaskins and Lill, ca. 1940
    24. Group of girls, ca. 1940
    25. Woman on porch, ca. 1940
    26. Ellen, Mami and Kachel, ca. 1940
    27. Young woman on porch steps, ca. 1940
    28. James W. Johnson, ca. 1940
    29. Young woman, ca. 1940
    30. Mrs. Charlotte Opperman, ca. 1940
    31. Young woman, ca. 1940
    32. Robert P. Daniel in uniform, ca. 1940
    33. Group of men and women, ca. 1940
    34. Unidentified woman, ca. 1940
    35. Group of men and women in front of church, ca. 1940
    36. Two men in front of house, ca. 1940
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 37-57 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    37. Mary Langley (West Point, Va.), 1950 Jan. 10
    38. Two unidentified women in garden, ca. 1950
    39. Lillian J. Dailey, ca. 1950
    40. Margaretta Dailey, ca. 1950
    41. Two unidentified women outdoors, ca. 1950
    42. Unidentified children (Crawford?) on porch, ca. 1940
    43. Unidentified children outdoors, ca. 1950
    44. Graduation of George W. Watkins, ca. 1950
    45. Graduation of Robert Prentiss David, ca. 1950
    46. Thelma Watkins and William Spurbock, ca. 1950
    47. Miss Storrs, ca. 1950
    48. Winfrey, ca. 1950
    49. Unidentified woman on porch, ca. 1950
    50. Unidentified man on porch, ca. 1950
    51. Three women outside of car in hats, ca. 1950
    52. Unidentified man outside, ca. 1950
    53. Young man and woman outside, ca. 1950
    54. Unidentified man on porch, ca. 1950
    55. Unidentified woman outside, ca. 1950
    56. Unidentified woman school photograph, ca. 1950
    57. Unidentified man out in front of house, ca. 1950
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 58-73 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    58. Two unidentified women, ca. 1950
    59. Young woman sitting on rock, ca. 1950
    60. Young woman in front of house, ca. 1950
    61. Young woman sitting by creek, ca. 1950
    62. Young woman in front of house, ca. 1950
    63. Graduation of an unidentified man, ca. 1950
    64. Class of 1939 N.K.T.S. Includes Josephine Pemberton, Thelma Beatrice Dixon, Edward Christian, James Clayton, Mr. Patterson, and Nellie Macon
    65. Christmas photograph card from the J. Andrew and Josephine Bowler, 1945
    66. Young man in uniform, ca. 1940-1950
    67. Young woman outside, ca. 1950
    68. Young family outside, ca. 1940-1950
    69. Mamie Franklin, ca. 1940-1950
    70. Young women and man outside of house, ca. 1940-1950
    71. Family outside underneath a tree, ca. 1940-1950
    72. George W. Watkins and Thelma Watkins in front of car, ca. 1940-1950
    73. Young man in uniform, ca. 1940-1950
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 74-92 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    74. Ruth, ca. 1940
    75. Unidentified man in front of house, ca. 1940
    76. Postcard of Reedville High and Elementary Schools, Reedville, Va., 1929
    77. Unidentified man and woman outside, ca. 1940
    78. Unidentified man and woman outside, ca. 1940
    79. Unidentified group outside, ca. 1940
    80. Young woman on porch steps, ca. 1940
    81. Young woman on lawn, ca. 1940-1950
    82. Young woman standing next to car, ca. 1940
    83. Walter J. Manning, ca. 1940
    84. Unidentified group on park bench, ca. 1940-1950
    85. Unidentified group on rock, ca. 1940-1950
    86. Unidentified group outside, ca. 1940-1950
    87. Group of young women outside, ca. 1940-1950
    88. Group of school children, ca. 1940-1950
    89. Man and woman outfront of house, ca. 1940-1950
    90. Unidentified man standing by tree, ca. 1940-1950
    91. Young woman in garden, ca. 1940-1950
    92. Young woman in garden, ca. 1940-1950
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 93-111 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    93. Group in front of school bus, ca. 1940-1950
    94. Man and two children outside, ca. 1940-1950
    95. Thelma and George W. Watkins, 28 July 1940
    96. Group in front of Elam Baptist Church, ca. 1940
    97. Man and two children outside, ca. 1940-1950
    98. Ms. Hawkins, Mary Murray, and Thelma Watkins, ca. 1940
    99. Lloyd Morse in uniform and dog, ca. 1940
    100. Mrs. Ellen Archer Stephens, ca. 1940
    101. PFC Lloyd Morse in the snow (Fort Myers, Va.), ca. 1940
    102. Two men in uniform, ca. 1940
    103. Glina Bowman, Thelma Watkins, and unidentified woman, ca. 1940
    104. Mrs. Carter-Hampton, ca. 1940
    105. Elam Church (Charles City, Va.), Christmas 1937
    106. Gertrude Spurlock, ca. 1930-1940
    107. Sedley D. Jones (Pops), ca. 1930-1940
    108. Young woman next to a truck, ca. 1940
    109. George W. Watkins and cousins, ca. 1940
    110. Two young children outside of building, ca. 1930-1940
    111. William Spurlock, ca. 1940
  - Photograph Album #10, Photos 112-138 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    112. Postcard photograph of George W. Watkins and unidentified female, ca. 1930-1940
    113. Gladys B. Jones and Bessie Edwards, 1921
    114. Elam Church (Charles City, Va.), ca. 1930
    115. Unidentified man outside with newspaper, ca. 1930
    116. Unidentified family outside on lawn, ca. 1930
    117. George W. Watkins and unidentified group, ca. 1930
    118. Drakhine and Bonnie, ca. 1930
    119. Student identification of Mary Davis, Virginia Union University, 1943-1944
    120. Mary Hawkins and unidentified woman outside, ca. 1930-1940
    121. Doris Strottier (age 20 months), Buffalo, New York, ca. 1930
    122. Unidentified family photograph, ca. 1930-1940
    123. James Sydnor Jr., in rockingchair on porch, ca. 1930-1940
    124. Four unidentified women in sailor shirts, ca. 1930-1940
    125. Four unidentified men and horses, ca. 1930-1940
    126. Unidentified family on porch steps, ca. 1940
    127. Unidentified women, ca. 1940
    128. Unidentified woman by bush, ca. 1940
    129. Two unidentified women in ocean, ca. 1940
    130. Three unidentified people outside, ca. 1940
    131. Unidentified family outside, ca. 1940
    132. Large group of unidentified, possibly teacher, ca. 1940
    133. Audrey Jones Braxton, ca. 1940
    134. Unidentified family outside, ca. 1940
    135. Unidentified family outside, ca. 1940
    136. Unidentified woman outside, ca. 1940
    137. Unidentified group outside, ca. 1940
    138. Unidentified school group, ca. 1940
  - Oversize photographs of Ebenezer Baptist Church (Richmond, Va.), ca. 1920-1930 and Martha Smith, ca. 1930. (Box 5, Folder 9)